<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="94">
    <author>apuehri</author>
    <version>1.0.0.0</version>
	
    <title>
		<en>Use Your Own License Plates</en>
		<de>Nutze Eigene Kennzeichen</de>
		<fr>Propres Plaques D'immatriculation</fr>		
    </title>
	
	<description>
		<en><![CDATA[use your own license plates

This mod allows you to use your own license plates on every map!

You can find detailed instructions on how to use your own license plates
after starting the game for the first time with the mod loaded
in the file -- useYourOwnLicensePlates_Help.txt -- in the "modSettings/FS25_useYourOwnLicensePlates" directory

The following license plates are prepared:
 - Austria (all 9 federal states, 2 license plate types)
 - Germany (federal state neutral, 4 license plate types)

When using the mod in an existing save game, you should reconfigure 
the license plates of your existing vehicles.
]]></en>

		<de><![CDATA[Nutze deine eigenen Kennzeichen

Dieser Mod ermöglicht es dir auf jeder Map deine eigenen Kennzeichen zu verwenden!

Eine genaue Anleitung wie du deine eigenen Kennzeichen nutzen kannst,
findest du nach erstmaligem Spielstart mit geladenem Mod
in der Datei -- useYourOwnLicensePlates_Help.txt -- im "modSettings/FS25_useYourOwnLicensePlates" Verzeichnis

Es sind folgende Kennzeichen vorbereitet:
 - Österreich (alle 9 Bundesländer, 2 Kennzeichentypen)
 - Deutschland (Bundeslandneutral , 4 Kennzeichentypen)

Bei Verwendung des Mods in einem bereits bestehenden Savegame, solltest du die Kennzeichen 
deiner bereits vorhandenen Fahrzeuge einmal neu konfigurieren.
]]></de>

      <fr><![CDATA[utilisez vos propres plaques d'immatriculation

Ce mod vous permet d'utiliser vos propres plaques d'immatriculation sur chaque carte!

Instructions détaillées sur la façon d'utiliser vos propres plaques d'immatriculation
Vous le trouverez après avoir démarré le jeu pour la première fois avec le mod chargé
dans le fichier -- useYourOwnLicensePlates_Help.txt -- dans le répertoire "modSettings/FS25_useYourOwnLicensePlates"

Les plaques d'immatriculation suivantes sont préparées :
 - Autriche (les 9 État fédéral, 2 types de plaques d'immatriculation)
 - Allemagne (état neutre, 4 types de plaques d'immatriculation)

Lorsque vous utilisez le mod dans une sauvegarde existante, 
vous devez utiliser les identifiants de votre partie existante
Reconfigurez les véhicules une fois.
]]></fr>
	</description>	
	
    <iconFilename>icon_useYourOwnLicensePlates.png</iconFilename>
	<multiplayer supported="true"/>

    <extraSourceFiles>
        <sourceFile filename="scripts/useYourOwnLicensePlates.lua"/>
    </extraSourceFiles>	

</modDesc>
